Welcome to my math skills to ACE
chemistry series. So, with this bunch of
videos, the whole idea here is to help
you prepare yourself for your chemistry
course, whether you're taking
introductory chemistry or general
chemistry 1 or even high school
chemistry. These are going to go over,
this playlist is really designed to go
over all the basic skills that you need
to be ready for your chemistry class and
hopefully even ace it. being that most
of the mathematical skills that you will
come across are found in this general
list that I'm going to be scrolling
through. So, we're going to be making
I'm going to be making a bunch of videos
that have to go over whether it's
counting and identifying sigfigs,
rounding of sigfigs, scientific
notation, basic algebra, SI units and
measurement, unit conversions,
especially that dimensional analysis
which will lead to stochometry one day.
um using something called least common
multiples which we'll see in balancing
chemical equations. How to use fractions
which have to do with stochometry
dimensional analysis percents. Um and
really trying to just like how can we
like even decode word problems how to
use your calculator which can be a
little scary especially if it's the
first time you've seen it maybe since
maybe high school or if that was a while
ago or maybe even just last summer maybe
it was it was some time ago. The whole
idea here is just to get you prepared so
that way you have these as a reference
for yourself. So when you're going
through all your different homeworks,
you can watch one of these short videos
to help you ace chemistry. So we will be
going through all these different videos
and I hope to see you soon in in the
different videos. Please leave comments,
like and subscribe and thank you so much
for watching. Bye.
[Music]